[OVERDO]
[Episode 29]
Stop there!
The government orders
to search the train station immediately.
The Marshal orders—
no one is allowed
to enter the train station.
Anyone who blocks us
will be punished by military law.
Stop!
Anyone who forces their way in
will be shot on sight.
Although the North-South Railway...
is no longer managed by my Li family,
Nancheng train station is still
the Ying Army's station.
Let me tell you,
without my permission,
you
cannot enter.
You can't take away
the things inside either.
Do you know what's inside?
So what?
The things inside
can keep my father safe.
When my father's not around,
the entire Ying Army
listens to my orders.
If you want to force your way in,
have a guess—
would I dare to get serious with you?
Li Boze, do you know
that if that thing spreads,
thousands of lives will be affected?
Li Rongzhang is only under investigation
and detention right now.
-As for which is more important—
-Of course my father is more important.
Look!
Look at that expression of yours.
In your heart,
anything can be more important
than family.
That's why you can make
our mother sick with anger,
be mad at our eldest sister,
and ignore our father's life and death!
But I'm different.
To me,
family is more important.
That's why I've
repeatedly let you do as you please.
It's different now.
Now that my father
is in a difficult position,
I can't let you mess around.
Or if you want to do anything,
you can try.
Fine.
Li Boze,
I don't have time to show off
my strength to you here.
I can leave the Red Pills behind.
But I must
take that patient away today.
He is the first infected person.
The Ying Army has no experience
in dealing with this.
If he stays
and is not treated properly,
it will only get everyone killed.
Bring him out.
Wait.
Let my men in.
I've already told you the dangers
of the Red Pill.
You better know
what you're doing.
[Li Residence]
Brother.
You work for the government,
and act as a dog for the Zhang family.
Do you
get double pay?
Why are you here?
Father.
Rest assured, Father.
The Ying Army is
operating as usual.
Don't worry too much.
This place is full of people
who seem to be from the government,
but are actually
the Zhang family's running dogs.
You came in so openly...
Did you use
the Zhang family's connections?
Yes.
I made a deal with Zhang Mingshu.
Tomorrow morning,
this batch of Red Pills will be sent away.
In the evening,
you will be reinstated
to your official position.
Bastard!
How could I give birth
to someone like you?
Although I play dirty,
I have never
colluded with others
to harm our compatriots.
Do you understand?
I don't want to know!
It's not my place
to care about these things!
All I need to do now
is to protect you,
and protect this family!
You are the future commander
of the Ying Army!
If you don't care, who will?
If you don't care about this,
what do you care about?
Is your head only full of petty romance?
Worthless thing.
Just like your mother.
Trash!
What I must do now
is only to keep you safe.
Why?
Because I only have you left, Father.
You are all I have now.
Foolish.
Foolish...
Get out.
Father.
No matter what,
I will protect you at all costs.
You seem
upset today, Father.
Rest early.
[Lanxin Theater]
The train station changed guards at night.
Now they are all Zhang family's men.
Young Master Boze
is really going to send the Red Pills out.
After Qingyu died,
he lost his mind.
Once this batch of Red Pills
leaves Nancheng,
their whereabouts will be hard to track.
So...
before the Red Pills are sent out,
we must dispose of them all.
Tomorrow,
our men will set up defenses in the city.
As soon as the train leaves the station,
blow it up immediately.
We absolutely cannot let the Red Pills
leave the city.
But we don't have enough men
or explosives.
Whether the train goes north or south,
or which route it takes—
we know nothing.
I know.
I know which route the Red Pills
will take tomorrow.
Susu.
How is Le'an?
Was he scared?
Kids are playful.
Reading a storybook for a while
made him forget his fear.
Susu.
About what happened 19 years ago,
I...
Between us,
it's been hard to tell
who's right or wrong for a while now.
At the end of the day,
we should both apologize to each other.
The most important thing right now
is to investigate the Red Pills.
I'll let you know if I hear anything.
Zhang Mingshu has a concubine
who came from the Renxin Orphanage.
She secretly sent someone to inform me.
[Nancheng Station] [Jiating Station]
[Qingqu Station] [Zhanan Station]
Tomorrow at 3 PM,
a train loaded with Red Pills
will depart along this railway.
The source is absolutely reliable.
This batch of Red Pills
is highly contagious.
So,
we absolutely cannot let this cargo
fall into the hands of the Zhang family.
So this batch of Red Pills is infected.
What's your plan now?
Tomorrow, our people
will set up defenses in the suburbs.
We'll blow up the train directly.
Who's going?
You and Ms. Ye go.
I will leave the people
at the aviation school to you.
Okay.
What about you?
I have to go to the train station.
I can't let Li Boze get on that train.
Besides,
I'm the one the Zhang family is targeting.
If I stay at the station
under their noses,
they can be relaxed.
I'll go check on Le'an.
According to our current plan,
the Red Pills should be exploded
as soon as they leave the station.
They won't even make it out of the city.
Why are you sending her and Ms. Ye away?
Nancheng is in danger.
I can't let them take risks.
The Pan-East Asia Chamber of Commerce
behind the Zhang family
is the vanguard
using trade activities to lead the way.
Their intentions are unpredictable.
Now the northern battlefield
has been lost,
even the higher-ups can't suppress them.
Me,
Li Boze,
and Li Rongzhang—
who among us will become
the first innocent soul under their guns?
Nobody knows.
Then why are you still going?
-The train station is full of their—
-Someone has to stand up.
[Nancheng Station] [Jiating Station]
[Qingqu Station] [Zhanan Station]
What are they singing?
I'm here all day long,
eating and sleeping.
It's so suffocating.
Do they think I'm made of cotton?
I'm being investigated,
not imprisoned.
If you make me uncomfortable,
none of you will have peace.
Go tell your master
to get someone who can relieve my boredom.
Get Hai Tangqing for me.
Go!
Understood.
[Nancheng Station]
The Young Marshal has ordered
a change of guards.
Return!
[Station entrance] [Station Exit]
[Nancheng Station]
Marshal,
I brought her here.
Are you satisfied?
Rest assured, Marshal.
We've already warned her.
She'll leave right after singing.
After all,
Boss Hai sings your favorite Liang Hongyu
the best.
All of you, get out.
Cooperate with me.
Thank you for escorting the cargo
and making this trip personally.
Young Master Mingshu said
as soon as the train leaves Nancheng,
the letter proving Marshal Li's innocence
will be delivered.
Li Boze!
[Nancheng Station]
What?
Trying to snatch the Red Pills?
These few men aren't enough.
I'll tell you one last time:
if this batch of Red Pills
leaves Nancheng,
there is no turning back.
I am the chief judge of the Red Pill case.
If Li Rongzhang
is truly innocent,
I can defend him.
Defend him?
Why are you pretending
to be a good person now?
It's too late.
But I truly understand now—
blood is thicker than water.
At least, no matter what,
Li Rongzhang will never abandon me.
[Nancheng Station]
The station is full of Zhang's men.
Please
be careful.
You've fought alongside me
for half my life.
You old comrades
should have been generals by now.
It's unfair to have you
pulling a rickshaw for me.
I was always meant
to pull the Marshal's rickshaw.
I've done it all my life.
This can be considered
seeing things through to the end.
You old man.
You still speak so bluntly.
Marshal,
let me go in your stead.
Some things,
I must handle myself.
How do you want me to cooperate?
I know you had a younger brother
who, 19 years ago,
was killed in an explosion.
Your true enemy
is the one who imprisoned me.
The railway explosion back then
was orchestrated by the Zhang family.
The Red Pill matter
cannot wait a single moment.
I've run the Ying Army for so many years.
Only I know certain places.
And some things,
only I can use.
I still have a few
old comrades from the early days
waiting for me at the station.
What's with that look?
I might not die.
Even if I do,
isn't that exactly what you want?
You will leave here safely.
Wait!
Why is it that the several times
I tried to assassinate you,
you let me go?
I once misunderstood
the mother of those two brats.
She hated me for half her life
and died leaving me behind.
There's really nothing to explain.
I owe her this.
I will go down
and apologize to her personally.
You're lucky.
Your eyes look like hers.
[Nancheng Station]
Li Boze,
do you know what you're doing?
Think about it—what you're doing now,
does it do justice to Qingyu
and your father's teachings?
Qingyu might not have done justice
to me either!
Laiyi.
What do you mean?
Don't you know?
Qingyu always knew
about the Red Pill's existence.
He had been
secretly investigating my father.
Even at his wedding,
he conspired with his fiancée
to assassinate my father.
You didn't know
any of this, did you?
Miss Fang,
have you seen this?
I found it in the wedding hall.
If an unexpected event
hadn't happened on that wedding day,
my father would have died long ago.
Yet I naively protected
this family for him,
taking care of his fiancée and your child.
With everything he did,
do you think he did right by me?
He never considered me
in the slightest.
I say he was a hypocrite,
and deserved to die a tragic death!
Say that again!
What?
I said he deserves a tragic death!
So what?
Are you trying to act tough with me here?
Fine, Li Boze.
I always thought
that guns shouldn't be pointed at family.
You're bold.
Come on.
If you have what it takes,
shoot and kill me today!
Second Brother.
How ridiculous.
The first time I hear you call me brother
is when you're forcing me to shoot you.
If it were in the past,
for this "Brother,"
I would do anything for you.
But now...
[Nancheng Station]
Farewell,
Marshall Li.
[Nancheng Station]
The pills...
My pills!
I know about you and that brat.
If you two really end up together,
consider this an early gift from me.
Take it.
This was the token of love
between his mother and me.
If I don't come back,
please help me persuade that boy.
♪ This spark of wildfire
spreading across the plains ♪
♪ Stirs embers that refuse to fade ♪
Persuade him not to
abandon his ideals because of me,
♪ I seize fate by the hand ♪
to uphold the nation's dignity
and know right from wrong,
♪ Accusing it of refusing to relent ♪
♪ Pain and joy blur before my eyes ♪
to not help the wicked,
and to return to the right path soon.
♪ Fate keeps replaying its endless cycle ♪
♪ The love that refused to die ♪
♪ Has already consumed us both ♪
Help them!
Hurry!
Where is the principal?
Where is Qingyi?
Seems to be over there.
Stay safe.
Qingyi!
How are you?
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Le'an is waiting for you.
I miss Le'an very much too.
And I miss...
Li Rongzhang is dead.
Li Rongzhang?
He detonated the black powder
that the Ying Army
hid in the underground tunnel.
I need to visit the Li family later.
After all,
he is also my father.
Go ahead.
We'll handle things here.
[Li Residence]
What should we do?
Exactly.
Yeah.
We are leaderless.
Enough.
Complaining won't help.
I say,
let's fight them.
Right.
I won't take their crap!
For the Marshal,
I'll risk my old life.
This is too much.
Young Marshal,
just give the order.
We hold the funeral
and handle my father's affairs first.
My father fought all his life,
but was wronged before he died.
After his death,
we can't panic
and ruin his reputation.
Uncle Tang.
Uncle Zhou.
You are my father's old comrades
and old friends.
Although my father is gone,
the Ying Army
cannot be in chaos.
Boze,
with us here,
rest assured.
The Ying Army
only listens to the Li family.
-Yes.
-We'll listen to the Li family.
Please go back first.
Boze.
My condolences.
You brat.
Hiding alcohol now?
Come.
Have a drink with me.
Remember:
if there's good alcohol,
let me drink it first.
No hiding alcohol.
Sure.
Come.